Finding Aid for the Herschel Burke Gilbert Papers PASC-M.0268
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Projects, Series 1.
  - The Bold and the Brave, Subseries 6.
    - The Bold and the Brave Vocal Parts, 12 pages; vocal parts (tenor,bass); 9.5 x 13 in.; photocopy of vocal parts, 10 staves (Box 7)
      Cue nos. 1A;10C (2 copies of 10C). Record no. 524. Sung by Sung by Mickey Rooney and Ross Bagdasarian.
    - The Sniper (cue title), 1955 July 19; 9 pages; 2fl,2,ob,2cl,bsn,accordian,3tpt,3tbn,tuba,perc,strings (6,6,0,6,2); 12.25 x 17.75 in.; manuscript ink full score, ozalid, 28 staves (Box 7)
      Cue no. 1B. Record no. 515.
    - Theme (Box 289)
      Theme from "The Bold and the Brave", music by Herschel Burke Gilbert, lyric by Alfred Perry, 3 pages
    - Theme Song, 6 pages; vocal lead sheet; 9 x 12 in.; glossy photographic copy, manuscript vocal leadsheet (Box 7)
      Record no. 530. 3 copies.
  - Bronco Apache, Subseries 117.
    - Tentative Budgets, 1953 (Box 258)
  - Burke's Law, Subseries 7.
    - Amos Burke, 1963 April 8; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 198)
      Tape reel: 1349. Log or Cue # 13204-13216. Alternate title for Burke's Law.
    - Burke's Law, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 210)
      Tape reel: 1413.
    - Burke's Law, 1964 September 4; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 211)
      Tape Reel: 1384. Log or Cue # 15458-15519.
    - Burke's Law, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 211)
      Tape Reel: 1393. Log or Cue # 14095 take 13 & take 4.
    - Correspondence re: Rights and Royalties, 1964 (Box 261)
      re: Joseph Mullendore and Buddy Baker
    - License (Box 288)
      License for Prod. #5812 - Who Killed Mr. X? (Burke's Law)
    - Notebook binder of Recording Logs, 1963-64: Burke's Law, The Rogues (Box 284)
    - Sound Recording, 1964 (Box 268)
    - Theme, 1963; 2 pages; 8 x 11.5 in.; printed music (Box 1)
      Record no. 597. p. 10-11 in Musik-Box, 172. Rolf Budde Musikverlage, Berlin. Studio: Four Star. Copyright owner: Four Star Television Music Co., Inc. Rolf Budde Musikverlag, 1963.
  - Cara Williams Show, Subseries 8.
    - Cara Williams, open reel audio tape (Box 184)
      Tape reel: 498.
    - Cara Williams, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 186)
      Tape Reel: 319.
    - Hello Cara, 1964 May; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 196)
      Tape reel: 1160.
  - Carmen Jones, Subseries 9.
    - Agreements, Cue Sheets, Correspondence (Box 258)
    - Assorted Materials (Box 288)
      Cigar box containing rubber stamps used to mark score of "Carmen Jones"
    - Conductor's Score, 9.5 x 12.5;13 x 17.5 in.; printed music with ms. Annotations (Box 8)
      Cue nos. Reel 1/1,1/2A-D,1/3,1/5-6,2/1-3,3/1,3/2A-B,3/3,4/1A-C,4/2,5/1,5/2A-B,5/3,6/1A-C1-2-3-4-5,6/2-3,7/2-3,8/1A-B,8/2-3,10/2-4,11/1,11/2A-B,3A,13/1,13/2A-B,13/3A,13/4A. Record no. 1664. Originally 13/4 was with these parts.
    - Conductor's Score, 9.5 x 12.5;13 x 17.5 in.; printed music with ms. Annotations (Box 9)
    - Conductor's Score, 9.5 x 12.5;13 x 17.5 in.; printed music with ms. Annotations (Box 10)
    - Conductor's Score, 9.5 x 12.5;13 x 17.5 in.; printed music with ms. Annotations (Box 11)
    - Conductor's Score, 9.5 x 12.5;13 x 17.5 in.; printed music with ms. Annotations (Box 12)
    - Conductor's Score, 9.5 x 12.5;13 x 17.5 in.; printed music with ms. Annotations (Box 13)
    - Conductor's Score, 9.5 x 12.5;13 x 17.5 in.; printed music with ms. Annotations (Box 14)
    - Contracts and Agreements (Box 288)
      Agreement between Twentieth Century Fox Film Corp & Herschel Burke Gilbert for "Carmen Jones"
    - Cue Sheet (Box 251)
      20th Century-Fox Film Corp cue sheet and continuity report.
    - Habanera (That's Love), 18 pages; 2altoxsax,2tenorsax,3tpt,2tbn,voice,piano,bass; 11.25 x 9 in; 11.25 x 9 in; 9.5 x 12.75 in.; manuscript black ink full score, 9 staves, ozalid; blue line copy of preceding ozalid, double sided pages; manuscript black ink piano conductor score ozalid, 10 staves (Box 117)
    - Lift 'em up an' put 'em down (cue title), 3 pages; vocal part; piano vocal score; 10 x 13 in; 9.5 x 12.5 in.; photocopy vocal part, one annotated, 8-10 staves (Box 117)
      Record no. 1967.
    - Orchestral Parts (Box 138)
      Record no. 2770.
    - Orchestral Parts (Box 139)
    - Orchestral Parts (Box 140)
    - Orchestral Parts (Box 141)
    - Orchestral Parts (Box 142)
    - Orchestral Parts (Box 143)
  - Comanche, Subseries 10.
    - Comanche, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 189)
      Tape Reel: 5.
    - Coral Records - Bob Thiele contract for "Comanche" album, 1958 (Box 268)
    - Correspondence (Box 251)
      Letter to Bob Thiele, Coral Records with information about songs for pending Comanche album.
    - Correspondence, Cue Sheets, 1955 (Box 258)
      Carl Krueger Productions
    - Full Score, 11 x 17 in.; photocopies of full scores (Box 15)
      Cue nos. 14843,14635,14643,14644,14634,14636,14842,14630,14631,14633,14627. Record no. 591.
    - Full Score, 11 x 17 in.; photocopies of full scores (Box 16)
    - Horns, 10B-1 14633 (Box 289)
    - Introducing Puffer (cue title), 1956 January 2; 3 pages; fl,ob,2cl,,tbn,perc,guitar,strings(5,5,6,4,2); 11.25 x 14.75 in.; manuscript pencil full score, red,black annotations, 18 staves (Box 15)
      Cue no. 3A. Record no. 547.
    - Puffer & Read Ride (cue title), 1956 January 1; 2 pages; fl,ob,2cl,2hns,2tpt,tbn,perc,guitar,strings(5,5,6,4,2); 11.25 x 14.75 in.; autograph pencil short score, red annotations, 14 staves (Box 15)
      Cue no. 14639. Record no. 551.
    - Puffer & Read Ride (cue title), 1956 January 1; 2 pages; fl,ob,2cl,2hns,2tpt,tbn,perc,guitar,strings(5,5,6,4,2); 11.25 x 14.75 in.; autograph pencil short score, red annotations, 14 staves (Box 16)
    - Quanah's Brother Faints (cue title), 3 pages; fl,Enghn,2cl,2hns,2tpt,tbn,perc, strings(6,6,6,4,2); 11.25 x 14.75 in.; manuscript pencil full score, red and black annotations,18 staves (Box 15)
      Cue no. 14642. Record no. 558.
    - Quanah's Brother Faints (cue title), 1956 January 3; 2 pages; 11.25 x 14.75 in.; autograph pencil short score, red annotations, 14 staves (Box 15)
      Cue no. 14642. Record no. 557.
    - Quanah's Brother Faints (cue title), 1956 January 3; 2 pages; 11.25 x 14.75 in.; autograph pencil short score, red annotations, 14 staves (Box 16)
    - Quanah's Brother Faints (cue title), 3 pages; fl,Enghn,2cl,2hns,2tpt,tbn,perc, strings(6,6,6,4,2); 11.25 x 14.75 in.; manuscript pencil full score, red and black annotations,18 staves (Box 16)
    - Record Album Correspondence, 1956 (Box 258)
    - Red Meets Marge (cue title), 4 pages; fl,ob,cl,hn,guitar,strings; 9.25 x 12.75 in.; manuscript ink conductor score, 12 staves (Box 15)
      Cue no. 4 A-2. Record no. 535.
    - Red Meets Marge (cue title), 4 pages; fl,ob,cl,hn,guitar,strings; 9.25 x 12.75 in.; manuscript ink conductor score, 12 staves (Box 16)
    - Reed Sees Cavalry (cue title), 1956 January 25; 7 pages; 2fl,ob,2cl,bsn,3hn,2tpt,3tbn,2perc, strings (7,7,6,4,3); manuscript full score, red and black annotations, 33 staves (Box 15)
      Cue no. 14842. Record no. 586. Found in a large envelope marked "Herschel Gilbert originals (scores) Recorded Munich Aug '61 [Cues] 14394-14843.
    - Reed Sees Cavalry (cue title), 1956 January 25; 7 pages; 2fl,ob,2cl,bsn,3hn,2tpt,3tbn,2perc, strings (7,7,6,4,3); manuscript full score, red and black annotations, 33 staves (Box 16)
    - The Last Handshake (cue title), 1956 January 19; 2 pages; 2 fl, 2 ob, 3 cl, bsn, 3 hn,3tpt,2tbn,marimba,3perc,guitar,strings(8,8,8,6,3); 11.25 x 17.5 in.; autograph black ink full score ozalid, 18 staves (Box 15)
      Cue no. 10 B-1. Record no. 536.
  - Crime and Punishment U.S.A., Subseries 11.
    - Beetles (cue title), 1958 December 26; 3 pages; 11 x 14.25 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 17)
      Cue no. 3B. Record no. 605.
    - Beetles (cue title), 1958 December 26; 3 pages; 11 x 14.25 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 18)
    - Burying Loot (cue title), 10.5 x 15.25 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 17)
      Cue no. 1C. Record no. 602.
    - Burying Loot (cue title), 10.5 x 15.25 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 18)
    - Cafe to Slap (cue title), 1959 January 13; 16 pages; 11 x 14.75; 10 x 15.25 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 17)
      Cue no. 4A. Record no. 610.
    - Cafe to Slap (cue title), 1959 January 13; 16 pages; 11 x 14.75; 10 x 15.25 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 18)
    - Cool Fugue, 1959 (Box 279)
      "Cool Fugue" song by Ernie Hughes from the motion picture "Crime & Punishment USA", record - music report
    - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 258)
      Correspondence related to recording the score and/or producing an album or single.
    - Correspondence, Cue Sheets, and Newspaper Clippings, 1960 (Box 258)
    - Crime and Punishment U.S.A, 1959 January 16; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 145)
      Tape Reels: 23-26.
    - Cue 5A, 1 pages; 12 x 14 in.; manuscript pencil sketch (Box 17)
      Cue no. 5A. Record no. 611.
    - Cue 5A, 3 pages; 11 x 14.5 in; manuscript pencil full score (Box 17)
      Cue no. 5A. Record no. 612.
    - Cue 5A, 3 pages; 11 x 14.5 in; manuscript pencil full score (Box 18)
    - Cue 5A, 1 pages; 12 x 14 in.; manuscript pencil sketch (Box 18)
    - Cue 8B, 4 pages; 11 x 14.5 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 17)
      Record no. 614.
    - Cue 8B, 4 pages; 11 x 14.5 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 18)
    - Did You Kill Your Wife (cue title), 2 pages; 12 x 14 in.; manuscript pencil sketch (Box 17)
      Cue no. 8B. Record no. 613.
    - Did You Kill Your Wife (cue title), 2 pages; 12 x 14 in.; manuscript pencil sketch (Box 18)
    - End Title, 4 pages; 10 x 15 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 17)
      Cue no. 10D. Record no. 616.
    - End Title, 4 pages; 10 x 15 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 18)
    - Enter Swanson (cue title), 1958 December 24; 4 pages; 11 x 14.5 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 17)
      Cue no. 3A. Record no. 604.
    - Enter Swanson (cue title), 1958 December 24; 4 pages; 11 x 14.5 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 18)
    - Full Score, 53 pages; 11.25 x 17.5 in.; autograph and manuscript black ink full score ozalids, 18 staves (Box 17)
      2A and 9B missing. 7AS,7A,7B,8A autographs. 1 A is the same as 5A. 9B is the same as 8A.Cue nos. 1A,1B,1C,3A,3B,4AA,4B,7AX,7A,7B,8A,10C,10D. Record no. 617.
    - Full Score, 11.5 x 17.25 in.; photocopy full scores (Box 17)
      Cue nos. 1A,1B,1C,3A,3B,4AA,4B,4C,7AX,7A,7B,8A,10C, 10D. Record no. 618.
    - Full Score, 53 pages; 11.25 x 17.5 in.; autograph and manuscript black ink full score ozalids, 18 staves (Box 18)
    - Full Score, 11.5 x 17.25 in.; photocopy full scores (Box 18)
    - Instrumental Breakdown, 1959 January 16; 3 pages; 0b,2sax,3tpt,4tbn,piano,guitar,2perc,strings (1,1,1,5,2); 11.25 x 18.75;11.5 x 14.25 in.; printed instrumental breakdown with ms and typed fill-ins; one ozalid (Box 17)
      Studio: T-D Enterprises, Inc.; Allied Artists. Record no. 598. According to this sheet, Gilbert composed and orchestrated Cues 2A,7AX,7A,7B,8A,9B so these copies of the full score ought to be autographs.
    - Instrumental Breakdown, 1959 January 16; 3 pages; 0b,2sax,3tpt,4tbn,piano,guitar,2perc,strings (1,1,1,5,2); 11.25 x 18.75;11.5 x 14.25 in.; printed instrumental breakdown with ms and typed fillins; one ozalid (Box 18)
    - Main Title, 1959 January 13; 19 pages; ob,alto and tenor sax, 3tpt,4 tbn,2 perc, piano, strings (1,1,1,5,1?); 11.75 x 15 in.; manuscript pencil full score, red annotations, 24 staves (Box 17)
      Cue no. 1A. Record no. 600.
    - Main Title, 1959 January 13; 19 pages; ob,alto and tenor sax, 3tpt,4 tbn,2 perc, piano, strings (1,1,1,5,1?); 11.75 x 15 in.; manuscript pencil full score, red annotations, 24 staves (Box 18)
    - Murderer (cue title), 1958 December 29; 4 pages; 10 x 15.25 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 17)
      Cue no. 4A. Record no. 608.
    - Murderer (cue title), 1958 December 29; 4 pages; 10 x 15.25 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 18)
    - Night Walk (cue title), 1959 January 3; 11 pages; ob,altsax,tensax,3tpt,4tbn,tymp,drum,piano,strings; 1.5 x 15.25 in.; autograph? pencil full score, red and blue annotations, 24 staves (Box 17)
      Cue title: 4B. Record no. 609.
    - Night Walk (cue title), 1959 January 3; 11 pages; ob,altsax,tensax,3tpt,4tbn,tymp,drum,piano,strings; 1.5 x 15.25 in.; autograph? pencil full score, red and blue annotations, 24 staves (Box 18)
    - Orchestral Parts, 9.5 x 14.75 in.; manuscript orchestral parts in folders listing instrumentation (Box 17)
      Cue nos. 1A,1B,1C,2A,3A,3B,3C,4AA,4B,4C,7A,7AX,7B,8A,8B,9A,9B,10A,10D,10C, Masters ozalids only perc and cello. Record no. 619.
    - Orchestral Parts, 9.5 x 14.75 in.; manuscript orchestral parts in folders listing instrumentation (Box 18)
    - Robert's Loot (cue title), 1959 January 1; 5 pages; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 17)
      Cue no. 1B. Record no. 601.
    - Robert's Loot (cue title), 1959 January 1; 5 pages; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 18)
    - Sketches, 4 pages; 9.5 x 12.5;10.5 x 13.25 in.; pencil sketches, miscellaneous (Box 17)
      Larger pages have page numbers 29 and 30.Record no. 599.
    - Sketches, 4 pages; 9.5 x 12.5;10.5 x 13.25 in.; pencil sketches, miscellaneous (Box 18)
    - Swanson Leaves Bob (cue title), 1 pages; 3ww,str.quartet,piano,bass,tpt, drum; 11 x 14 in.; autograph pencil sketch, 12 staves (Box 17)
      Cue no. 3C. Record no. 606.
    - Swanson Leaves Bob (cue title), 3 pages; 11 x 14.25 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 17)
      Cue nos. 3C, 10A. Record no. 607.
    - Swanson Leaves Bob (cue title), 3 pages; 11 x 14.25 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 18)
    - Swanson Leaves Bob (cue title), 1 pages; 3ww,str.quartet,piano,bass,tpt, drum; 11 x 14 in.; autograph pencil sketch, 12 staves (Box 18)
    - Swanson's Suicide (cue title), 12 pages; 10.5 x 15 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 17)
      Cue no. 10C. Record no. 615.
    - Swanson's Suicide (cue title), 12 pages; 10.5 x 15 in.; manuscript pencil full score (Box 18)
    - Zow-Wez-Nee (cue title), 4 pages; 9.5 x 12;11 x 14.75 in.; manuscript pencil full score; manuscript pencil instrumental leadsheet (Box 17)
      Pages numbered 1,3,5. Gimmick version. Cue no. 1D. Record no. 603.
    - Zow-Wez-Nee (cue title), 4 pages; 9.5 x 12;11 x 14.75 in.; manuscript pencil full score; manuscript pencil instrumental leadsheet (Box 18)
  - Death Valley Days, Subseries 12.
    - Correspondence, 1956-1966 (Box 252)
      Includes official copyright doc of John Paul Music for Death Valley Days TV Series
    - End Title, 3 pages; fl,ob,3tpt,4tbn,2perc.Spanish guitar,banjo,strings (6,6,0,4,2); 11.25 x 17.5 in.; photocopy full score (Box 19)
      Cue no. 3C. Record no. 623.
    - Letter from TVT Records regarding ownership and use of The Detectives theme and Death Valley Days theme (Box 251)
    - Main Title, 1964 September 13; 4 pages; fl,ob,3tpt,4tbn,1perc,Spanish guitar, banjo,strings (6,6,0,4,1); 11.25 x 17.5 in.; photocopy full score (Box 19)
      Cue no. 1A. Record no. 622.
    - Main Title, 2 pages; piano sketch; 10 x 12.5 in.; autograph pencil sketch, annotations in red, 10 staves (Box 19)
      Record no. 620.
    - Music Cue Sheets (Box 282)
      mostly Death Valley
    - Music Cue Sheets, Bills, Licenses (Box 282)
    - Script (Box 281)
      TV Script, Death Valley Days: Fifteen Paces to Fame by Jacquiline Rhodes, Production No. 395
    - Twenty Mule Train, 1956 May 6; 3 pages; piano vocal; 10 x 13 in.; photocopy piano vocal score (Box 19)
      multiple copiesRecord no. 621.
  - The Detectives Starring Robert Taylor, Subseries 13.
    - Cue Sheets (Box 237)
    - Cue Sheets (Box 252)
    - Cue Sheets (Box 282)
    - Detectives, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 186)
      Tape Reel: 315.
    - Financial Papers, 1963-1966 (Box 268)
      Dot Records Inc. - "The Rifleman" theme and "The Detectives" themes
    - Letter from TVT Records regarding ownership and use of The Detectives theme and Death Valley Days theme (Box 251)
    - Robert Taylor, 1963 September 22; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 176)
      Tape reel: 1121. Log or Cue# 8855.
    - Robert Taylor Detectives, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 186)
      Tape Reel: 314. Log or Cue#2812A-2813C.
    - Robert Taylor Detectives, open reel audio tape (Box 187)
      Tape reels: 312, 313. Log or Cue #2814A-2815C-X8, 2813AX1-2813CX15.
  - Diamond City, Subseries 116.
    - Main Title, Finances (Box 258)
  - Dick Powell Show, Subseries 14.
    - Boston Terrier (episode title), open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 184)
      Tape reels: 482, 483, 484. Log or Cue #8412-8442, 8462-8472, 8473-8486.
    - Correspondence from Jimmie Haskell to HB Gilbert re: ASCAP and Dick Powell Show Cues (Box 251)
    - Dick Powell, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 186)
      Tape Reel: 317.
    - Dick Powell, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 187)
      Tape reel: 284.
    - Luxury Liner (episode title), 1963 January 31; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 206)
      Tape reel: 1125.
  - The Durante Show, Subseries 16.
    - Durante Pilot, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 180)
      Tape reel: 501. Log or Cue #4363-10241.
  - The Four Seasons, Subseries 19.
    - Correspondence re: Rights and Royalties, 1964 (Box 261)
      Correspondence re: "Yancy Derringer Cues" AKA "Four Seasons" (by Gilbert/Russell)
  - From Hell It Came, Subseries 106.
    - Assignment of Rights (Box 241)
    - Music, 1957 August 8 (Box 248)
      John Paul Music for From Hell It Came, Milner Bros. production released through Allied Artists Pictures Corp.
    - Sync license by American Contemporary Entertainment for background music, 1981 (Box 253)
  - The Gemini Affair, Subseries 21.
    - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 259)
      Moonstone Productions
    - Gemini Affair, 1974 May 24; open reel audio tapes; 15 ips. (Box 182)
      Tape reels: 560-561.
  - Gene Barry Sings of Love and Things, Subseries 127.
    - Photographs, 1964 (Box 269)
      Gene Barry, first album "Gene Barry Sings ... of love and things" 1964, includes 3 x 5 black and white photographs of Gilbert and Gene Barry
    - Sound Recording, 1964 May 7; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 171)
      Tape Reel: 925.
    - Sound Recording, 1964 March 1; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 171)
      Tape Reel: 923.
  - Geronimo, Subseries 119.
    - Correspondence,Choral Score, Cue Sheets, 1962 (Box 259)
  - The Getter and the Holder, Subseries 125.
    - Assorted Materials, 1965 November (Box 254)
      "The Getter and the Holder", original script by Sam Neuman, scores by Herschel Gilbert for "A Dirty Dollar in a Nice Clean Hand", "Every Body Needs Something" and "The Law of Supply and Demand."
  - Gilligan's Island, Subseries 22.
    - Gilligan's Island, open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 175)
      Tape reel: 1113. Log or Cue# 5820-5858.
    - Gilligan's Island, open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 176)
      Tape reel: 1117. Log or Cue# S-46 thru ?
  - The Girl in My Heart, Subseries 23.
    - Assorted Materials (Box 254)
      There's A Girl in My Heart: music recording breakdown and schedules, agreements re: rights, correspondence, list of singers, cue sheets, financial papers, lyrics
  - Goldilocks and the Three Bears, Subseries 1.
    Also called, "Mother Goose Land."
    - "Goldilocks and Three Bears" also called "Mother Goose Land": "Baby Bear's Christmas Wish", "Eeny and Meeny", "Little Red Riding Hood" & "Jack & the Beanstalk" (Box 260)
    - Christmas Music (episode title), 2 pages; 3 vl,vla,pianp,harp,perc.; 12 x 14 in.; autograph manuscript full score, black and red pencil, 12 staves (Box 117)
      Production no. 200. Cue no. 1B. Record no. 1934. 2 originals.
    - Goldilocks Wishes (episode title), 1 pages; 12 x 14 in.; autograph music manuscript full score, red and black pencil, 12 staves (Box 117)
      Production no. 200. Cue no. 3I. Record no. 1940.
    - Goldilocks Wishes (episode title), 2 pages; bassoon,percussion,celeste,harp,4 violins,viola,cello,bass; 11 x 14 in.; autograph music manuscript full score, red and black pencil, 20 staves (Box 117)
      Production no. 200. Cue no. 3I. Record no. 1939. 2 originals.
    - Logs, 1950 (Box 258)
      Logs for "Baby Bear's Christmas Wish" and "Eeny and Meeny"
    - Old King Cole (episode title), 1 pages; flute,clarinet,bassoon,trumpet,percussion,piano,harp,3violins,viola,cello,bass; 11 x 14 in.; autograph music manuscript full score, red and black pencil, 20 staves (Box 117)
      Production no. 200. Cue no. 1D. Record no. 1935.
    - Porridge Too Hot (episode title), 2 pages; 12 x 14 in.; autograph music manuscript full score, red and black pencil, 12 staves (Box 117)
      Production no. 200. Cue no. 1C. Record no. 1936. 2 originals.
    - Who's in My Chair (episode title), 2 pages; fl,cl,bsn,tpt,accordian,perc,piano,harp,strings; 9.5 x 12.5;12 x 14 in; autograph pencil sketch, red annotations, 12 staves; jackets for orchestral parts (Box 1)
      Production no. 200. Cue no. 3H. Record no. 1341. Folder title: Baby Bear's Christmas Wish. Sketch.
  - Gunsmoke, Subseries 25.
    - Gunsmoke, 1964 November 13 - 1965 March 5; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 205)
      Tape reels: 1104, 1105, 1106, 1107. Log or Cue #s: 6491-6554, 6555-6601, 6602-6641, 3657-3669, respectively.
  - Has Anybody Here Seen Chris, Subseries 27.
    - Agreements, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 259)
    - Has Anybody Here Seen Chris, 1968 April 22; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 145)
      Tape Reel: 27.
    - Has Anybody Here Seen Chris, open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 147)
      Tape Reel: 35.
    - Music Timings, Lyrics (Box 259)
    - Has Anybody Here Seen Chris, open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 144)
      Tape Reels: 31 and 33-34.
    - I Got Love, open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 144)
      Tape Reel: 32.
  - The Highwayman, Subseries 28.
    - Agreements and Music Recording Breakdown, 1951 (Box 259)
    - Cue M 101, 5 pages; 9.5 x 11.75 in.; autograph pencil short score, red annotations, 12 staves (Box 31)
      Cue no. M101. Record no. 686.
    - Cue Numbers M100-102,M200-202,M300,M402-4,M500,M600,M600A-B,M601-2,M700-1,M800,M900-1, 2 pages; strings (5,5,4,4,2),2fl,ob,cl,bsn,3hn,2 tpt,tbn,perc,hpschd; 11.5 x 17.5 in.; instrumental breakdown (Box 31)
      Record no. 682.
    - Dead or Alive (cue title), 1951 April 13; 2 pages; fl,ob,hn,harpsichord, strings (3,3,2,1,1); 9.5 x 11.75 in.; autograph pencil short score, 12 staves, red annotations (Box 31)
      Cue no. M200. Record no. 688.
    - Empty Jackets for Orchestral Parts, 9.5 x 12.5 in. (Box 31)
      For cue nos. M202,300,301,400 (401),402,500(501),600A,600B,601,602,900. Record no. 683. Eleven jackets, each jacket has the cue title and instrumentation, time, and numbers of players.
    - Main Title, 3 pages; 11 x 17 in.; photocopy of short score (Box 31)
      Cue no. 14850. Record no. 684.
    - The Last Ride, 3 pages; 11 x 17 in.; photocopy of short score (Box 31)
      Cue no. 14851. Record no. 685.
    - The Scarf (cue title), 1951 April 13; 1 pages; fl,ob,hn,harpsichord, strings (3,3,2,1,1); 9.5 x 10.75 in.; autograph pencil short score, 12 staves, red annotations (Box 31)
      Cue no. M102. Record no. 687.
  - Honey West, Subseries 29.
    - Honey West, 1966 January 18; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 161)
      Tape Reel: 897. Log or Cue# 21530-21543.
    - Honey West, 1966 January 17 - 18; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 162)
      Tape reels: 898, 899. Log or Cue #21530-21543, 21544-21547.
    - Honey West, 1966 January 17; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 165)
      Tape Reels: 801-802. Log or Cue# 21520-21529.
    - Honey West, open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 165)
      Tape Reel: 803. Log or Cue# 18760-18767.
    - Honey West, 1965 July 30; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 167)